Hello everyone my name is Alana Bridgewater.
大家好我是 Alana Bridgewater
And I am, in fact, the singer of the King Dice song on the video game cuphead.
事实上我是茶杯头游戏里King Dice主题曲的演唱者
Now I know a lot of you do not believe that a woman is singing that.
我现在知道有很多人不相信这是女性唱出来的声音
But I can assure you that it is my voice.
但我能向你保证这是我的声音
注:
这个频道是Alana Bridgewater Gaming，
根据视频简介似乎是一周之内就突破了1000个订阅
When I get a thousand subscribers on this channel,
当我这个频道有了1000个订阅者的时候
we will be posting a live version with my band of the King Dice song.
我们乐队就会发布一个King Dice主题曲的现场版
So I look forward to getting to know you all, tell people about it.
所以我希望你们能了解并多多扩散这件事
And come back and see me soon.
然后再持续关注我的新动态
Thank you!
谢谢大家
It's not over yet.
这还没完呢